pchell.com 2019-03-10

# PC Hell: Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy for www.pchell.com  

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at [mark@webtrail.com](mailto:mark@webtrail.com). 

At www.pchell.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected by www.pchell.com and how it is used. 

###  Log Files

Like many other Web sites, www.pchell.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

### Email Newsletter

PCHell.com does have an email newsletter that collects your name and email address for distribution. The mailing list is controlled by Aweber and every newsletter has an option at the bottom to unsubscribe from the newsletter. The subscriber information for the newsletter is never sold to outside contacts and is only used for the purpose of distributing the ezine.

###  Cookies and Web Beacons 

www.pchell.com does not use cookies. 

###  DoubleClick DART Cookie 

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.pchell.com.  
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.pchell.com and other sites on the Internet.   
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include:

Google Adsense  
Commission Junction  
Clickbank  
Chitika  
Linkshare  
Amazon  
Kontera

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.pchell.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

www.pchell.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.pchell.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

### Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance 

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

### Contacting Us 

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

PCHell.com  
912 Mayfair Lane  
Grants Pass, OR 97527  
US  
mark@webtrail.com

### Changes to our Privacy Policy 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on 08/14/2011
